Eduardo Gomez

Chula Vista, CA • https://www.eduardogomez.dev/ • linkedin.com/in/gomezee eddieegomez4@gmail.com • +1 619-289-1591

Software Engineer

With over 5 years of experience, I have consistently improved team efficiency by 28% and increased user retention rates by 12%. In just 1 month, I developed an MVP that secured next round of funding for a startup. I also integrated blockchain technology into Full Stack Applications, resulting in a 22% increase in user earnings in just 10 months.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Zeal • Full-time • 05/2021 - 09/2023

Software Engineer III

- Consulting firm dedicated to colloborating with cross-functional team's to provide top-tier, usercentric solutions for client's.
- Consistently improved team efficiency by 28% through development and maintenance of critical internal tools.
- Ensured smooth user interaction and increased customer satisfaction by transforming design mockups into interactive and responsive web components.
- Implemented key features and enhancements, boosting user engagement and retention by 12% through resolving a critical bug related to authentication refresh tokens.
- · Developed MVP in just 1 month, resulting in next round of funding for startup.

C47 STUDIOS • California • Full-time • 11/2020 - 05/2021

Streaming and Video Production Company.

Full Stack Developer

- Designed and implemented an engaging redesign of the landing page, boosting user engagement by 25% and retention by 20%.
- Contributed in the development of MVP streaming platform for live events.

Alexandria.io • Full-time • 10/2019 - 08/2020

Full Stack Developer

- Facilitated direct payments and improved financial transactions by integrating blockchain technology into Full Stack Applications built on Open Index Protocol, resulting in increased security and trust for the business.
- Increased user earnings by 22% with a FLO & RVN coin crypto bot built with React, Node, and external APIs.

EDUCATION

Data Structures

Free Code Camp • 12/2019

CS50

edX • 12/2019

Responsive Web Design

Free Code Camp • 12/2018

Bachelor Degree

California State University • Chico, CA, USA • 12/2017

SKILLS

Amazon Web Services, Collaborative Environment, Comprehensive, Cross Functional Skills, CSS, Database Publishing, Facilitate, FastAPI, Flask Framework, JavaScript, Lambda, Minimum Viable Product, Mobile Application Development, MySQL, Next.js, NodeJS, Planning Process, Product Launch, Python, Ruby on Rails, Ruby Programming Language, Software Engineering, Streamlining Process, Team Productivity, TypeScript, User Authentication, User Engagement, User Interface Design, Web Application